auctus.org 2019-06-08

# AUCTUS’ PRIVACY POLICY

                                       AUCTUS’ PRIVACY POLICY
Last updated: May 22, 2019
This Privacy Policy (the “​Policy​”) has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how
AUCTUS PROJECT INC, a company incorporated under the laws of British Virgin Islands (​“Auctus”,
“we”, “us”, “our”, ​the “Company”​), uses personal information, inter alia, information that can be used to
directly or indirectly identify them (​“Personal Data”, “Personal Information”​), which they might supply to
us when they access or visit ​https://auctus.org/ website (the ​“Website”​). "You" refers to you, as a user of
the Website.
For the reason of the applicable legislation, we inform you that AUCTUS PROJECT INC is the data
controller of your Personal Information.
1. YOUR CONSENT
By using this Website, you consent to our collection and use of your Personal Information as described in
this Privacy Policy. The Company’s Privacy Policy applies to individuals and all other users of the Website
to ensure we carry out our services on your behalf and carry out the necessary relevant due diligence to
reduce fraud, money laundering and terrorism financing. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy,
along with related procedures, at any time, without providing any personal notice of the changes to you.
2. COLLECTING AND USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
We collect information from you when you register on our Website, subscribe to our service, respond to a
survey, fill out a form or enter information on our Website, participate in discussion boards or other social
media functions on our Website, enter a competition, promotion or survey, by corresponding with us by
phone, e-mail or otherwise, contribute to our Token Sale (as defined in the Terms of AUC Token Sale) and
when you report a problem with our Website or provide us with a feedback.
3. PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT IS COLLECTED AUTOMATICALLY
When you use our Website or use our products, we collect the Personal Data sent to Auctus by your PC,
mobile phone, or other access device. We collect the following information:
     ● Technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer
         to the Internet, your login information (if applicable), information about your visit, including the full
         Uniform Resource Locators (URL), clickstream to, through and from our Website (including date
         and time), information you viewed or searched for, page response times, download errors, length
         of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouseovers),
         methods used to browse away from the page and any information of yours related to contact our
         customer service team (e.g. phone number).
     ● Information we receive from other sources. This is information we receive about you from public
         domain, third parties or other websites we operate or the other services we provide. Third parties
                                                                                                                1

         we work with include business partners, subcontractors in technical, payment and delivery
         services, advertising networks, analytics providers, search information providers and credit
         reference agencies).
4. PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT IS UNIQUE TO YOU
Except for the information which is collected automatically, as described in the clause 3 of this Policy
above, the Personal Information is collected only when voluntarily offered by you. The Personal Information
means any information that is unique to you, such as:
     ●   Name;
     ●   Date of birth;
     ●   Name of entity you represent, if applicable;
     ●   Password, if any;
     ●   Your ETH wallet address (cryptocurrency address of your public ETH wallet address);
     ●   ETH amount you wish to transfer;
     ●   E-mail address;
     ●   Country and address of residence;
     ●   Other personal information you choose to provide.
By providing us your Personal Information, you also consent for us to collect, hold, use and disclose your
Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. In addition to providing the foregoing
information, if you choose to correspond further with us through e-mail or through the “contact” section of
our Website, we may retain, use or disclose the content of your messages together with your e-mail
address and our responses, unless otherwise agreed between you and the Company in written.
5. KNOW YOUR CUSTOMER PROCESS
In order to participate in the Token Sale, each prospective participant shall be obliged to undergo the
identification procedure. In certain cases (when additional verification is required by applicable laws, our
anti-money laundering and counter terrorism financing (“AML”) policies) Auctus may require you to provide
certain additional information for the due diligence purposes. We may request you to provide the following
information for the identification and AML purposes, inter alia:
     ●   Passport or other official document that can be used to identify you;
     ●   Numbers that you may use or have registered with your local tax authority;
     ●   Utility bills or other documents confirming your address;
     ●   Photographs of you;
     ●   Additional contact information (e.g. phone number, skype);
     ●   Source of your funds used for purchasing AUC tokens.
Auctus reserves the right to request basic Personal Data, described in the Article 4, and conduct
identification and AML procedures prior to your purchase of AUC tokens and/or use of any services,
                                                                                                           2

available through the Website. Your participation in the AUC token sale shall always be subject to the KYC
procedures, if applicable. At that, we shall not bear any liability for such possible incomplete user.
Auctus may refuse your access to the Website or AUC token sale in case (a) you refuse or fail to provide
information required for the identification purposes, or data required as a part of the AML procedures, or
(b) it has doubts as to the validity, authenticity and genuineness of the Personal Data, provided by you.
Auctus reserves the right to use a third party provider’s services for the purposes of conduction of
identification and AML procedures as provided herein. If this is the case, You will be redirected to the third
party provider’s website where you will be able to submit your Personal Information and other data required
for the identification and AML purposes; such third party provider shall verify the documents and
information provided. Please note that such third party provider may have a privacy policy which, in this
case, will regulate the relationship between You and such third party service provider.
6. COOKIES
When you access the Website or use Auctus products or services, we (or Google Analytics or similar
service provider on our behalf) may place small data files called “cookies” on your computer or other
device. Auctus uses these technologies to recognize you as our Token Sale Participant or user of the
Website, customize the Website and advertising, measure promotional effectiveness and collect
information about your computer or other access device to mitigate risks, help prevent fraud, and promote
trust and safety. You may control the use of cookies within your internet browser’s settings. If you reject or
delete certain cookies, be aware that the performance of the related features and functions of the Website
and its services may be impaired.
7. THE PURPOSE OF USING PERSONAL INFORMATION
We may use the Personal Information we collect from you for the following purposes:
●    Provision of services to you through the Website or the Auctus Platform;
●    Conducting the white listing process (for participants of the AUC token sale);
●    Verifying that you are the person who you say you are;
●    Conduction of the AUC Token sale, distribution of AUC tokens (which includes the use of your
     Personal Data in the smart contract and ETH blockchain);
●    Communicating with you about Auctus project, token sale, our products and services, news, events
     and other data which might be interesting to you in our opinion;
●    Maintenance, delivery and improvement of the Website, products and services provided through it;
●    Detecting, investigating and preventing fraudulent transactions and other illegal activities, and to
     protect the rights and property of the Auctus and others;
●    Analyzing ​and tracking data to determine the effectiveness of marketing campaign, usefulness of
     certain content or features, and for better understanding of users’ activity;
●    Notifying you about changes to the Website, terms of AUC token sale, user documentation, our
     products or services;
●    Protecting our rights and rights of the third parties;
                                                                                                             3

● Verifying compliance with the Terms of Use, governing the use of the Website.
8. HOW WE SECURE INFORMATION TRANSMISSIONS
Auctus protects your Personal Data under internationally acknowledged standards, using physical,
technical, and administrative security measures to reduce the risks of loss, misuse, unauthorized access,
disclosure, and alteration. Some of the safeguards Auctus uses are firewalls and data encryption, physical
access controls to our data centers, and information access authorization controls.
Auctus will ensure that the Personal Data will be stored and processed with the reasonable level of care
and security. Our corporate values, ethical standards and policies are committed to the protection of
customer’s Personal Data.
9. THIRD-PARTY DISCLOSURE
Auctus will not sell or rent your Personal Data to third parties. We are sometimes required to compare the
Personal Data you provide to third party databases in order to verify its accuracy and confirm your identity.
Auctus reserve the right to share your Personal Data with:
    ● Auctus banking and brokerage partners, legal, marketing, strategic and financial advisors, on a
        “need to know” basis;
    ● Company that develops, operates and maintains the Auctus Platform;
    ● Auctus Personal Data processing counter-parties or agents, hired by or cooperating with us, who’s
        services are required by us from the practical and business point of view;
    ● Companies that Auctus plan to merge with or be acquired by;
    ● Third party identification service providers for fraud prevention process, AML, CTF procedures;
    ● Law enforcement, governments officials or other third parties when Auctus is compelled to do so by
        any applicable law or a court order, or similar legal procedure; or Auctus believes in good faith that
        the disclosure of Personal Data is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial lose, to report
        suspect illegal activity or to investigate violations of any of our policies;
    ● Third parties, when aggregate information is disclosed, which cannot be reasonably used to
        identify you;
    ● Other third parties, only with your prior consent or direction to do so.
Please note that the above allows us to comply with relevant anti-money laundering and counter terrorism
financing (AML) regulations.
We use Mailchimp (​https://mailchimp.com​), developed and operated by the Rocket Science Group LLC
d/b/a MailChimp, a State of Georgia (USA) limited liability company, to store email addresses and automate
mailing campaigns. Your e-mail address may be transferred to Mailchimp. Please note that the e-mail
address on its own does not reasonably allow third parties to identify you.
We may also transfer your Personal Data to an entity from our group of companies, which develops,
operates and maintains the Auctus Platform. This is reasonably required in order to provide you with
                                                                                                             4

access to the Auctus Platform and allow you to receive certain services through the platform. Some of your
Personal Data may be made public by uploading to Ethereum blockchain or smart contract for the purposes
of the AUC Token Sale.
You agree that we may, for the purposes set out in article 7 above, permit the transfer of your Personal
Data to any jurisdiction, whether or not inside the European Economic Area, and that by accepting these
T&Cs you authorize and expressly consent to the processing of your Personal Data by us, our agents
and/or our service providers, provided that where your Personal Data is processed by entities other than
us, our agents or our service providers, we shall seek your prior written consent in respect of such
processing (unless your consent is granted under another provision of this Policy or other agreement
entered into between you and the Company).
10. THIRD-PARTY LINKS
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our Website.
These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility
or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of
our Website and welcome any feedback about these sites. Please check these policies before you submit
any Personal Data to these websites or use these services. It is also important to note that we allow
third-party behavioral tracking. We use Google Analytics and conversion tracking on the Website.
11. SOCIAL SHARING
The Website may allow you to share certain content from the Website on a social media or network. In
case you share the content or information through a social media or network, you become involved in
relations with the third party that provides the social media or network. Please visit the privacy policies of
such third parties to obtain more information about the purpose and scope of data collection and the
processing of such data by such entities. We do not bear any responsibility for such third parties.
12. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
Any changes we make to our Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where
appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. The date of last update can be viewed in the “Last Updated” field of
this Policy. It is your obligation to periodically visit the Website to review any changes that may be made to
this Policy. Your continued usage of the Website shall mean your acceptance of those amendments.
13. RETAINING OF THE INFORMATION
In accordance with applicable AML and CTF laws, and as needed to provide services to the users of the
Auctus Platform, we shall retain your Personal Data. This requirement is conditioned by the need of
complying with legal obligations and resolving possible disputes.
It is required by the law that Auctus retains a certain portion of your Personal Data for at least 5 years after
the end of AUC Token Sale. Herewith, we reserve the right to retain all of your Personal Data for the
                                                                                                                  5

abovementioned period as we will need to identify you and grant you access to the Auctus Platform, and
this may be reasonably needed for commercial purposes of our business and the Auctus Platform.
14. ACCESS TO THE INFORMATION, WITHDRAWAL
You have the right to withdraw your consent for collection, processing and storage of your Personal Data
by us at any time, unless we are directed to retain such information by the law. The withdrawal of consent
shall not affect the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal. If you decide to do
this, you should send the respective notification to us by e-mail or through the contact form on the Website.
You have the right to access Personal Information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in
accordance with the applicable laws and this Policy. You have the rights to obtain from us a confirmation as
to whether or not your Personal Data are being processed, and, where that is the case, access to the
personal data, including, (a) purposes of the processing, (b) the categories of Personal Data concerned, (c)
the recipients or categories of recipient to whom the Personal Data have been or will be disclosed, in
particular recipients in third countries or international organizations, (d) the envisaged period for which the
personal data will be stored, or the criteria used to determine that period, (e) the existence of the right to
request rectification or erasure of Personal Data or restriction of processing of your Personal Data, (f) the
right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, (g) if Personal Data are not collected from you, any
available information as to their source, (h) the existence of automated decision-making, including profiling,
and, at least in those cases, meaningful information about the logic involved, as well as the significance
and the envisaged consequences of such processing for you. Such information shall be provided upon your
request within 1 months from its receipt by us.
You may access, review and edit your Personal Data at any time by communicating Auctus in writing. You
have the right to demand Auctus to provide you access to your Personal Data and to require the correction,
updating or deletion of incorrect or/and inaccurate data by contacting Auctus. Nevertheless, this request
must comply with Auctus legal obligations. Auctus reserves its right to suspend provision of any services to
you referring to Auctus project and AUC token sale, and/or delete your account on the Website without
prior notice, not providing any compensation to you.
You may opt out of receiving promotional communications from us at any time by following the instructions
in those communications. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional communications, such as
technical notices, support or administrative notifications or information about your account (if you have
one).
You may lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority in case you believe that our actions violate your
rights as to the Personal Data.
15. THE RIGHT TO DATA PORTABILITY
You have the right to receive the Personal Data concerning you, which you have provided to Auctus, in a
structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and have the right to transmit those data to
another controller without hindrance from Auctus. In exercising this right, you shall have the right to have
                                                                                                              6

the Personal Data transmitted directly from us to another controller, in case we reasonably find this
technically feasible. Please note that execution of this right must not adversely affect the rights and
freedoms of others.
16. THE RIGHT TO BE FORGOTTEN
You have the right to obtain from Auctus the erasure of your Personal Data without undue delay where one
of the following grounds applies: ​(a) the Personal Data are no longer necessary in relation to the purposes
for which they were collected or otherwise processed, (b) you withdraw your consent for the processing and
there is no other legal ground for the processing, (c) you object to the processing where your Personal Data
are processed for direct marketing purposes, which includes profiling to the extent that it is related to such
direct marketing, (d) the Personal Data have been unlawfully processed, (e) the Personal Data have to be
erased for compliance with a legal obligation in the law to which you are the subject.
We may reject your request for erasure in case the processing of your Personal Data is necessary (i) for
exercising the right of freedom of expression and information, (ii) for compliance with a legal obligation
which requires processing by the law to which Auctus is subject or for the performance of a task carried out
in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in us, (iii) for archiving purposes in the
public interest, scientific or historical research purposes or statistical purposes in accordance with the law in
so far as the right for erasure is likely to render impossible or seriously impair the achievement of the
objectives of that processing; or (iv) for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims.
17. THE RIGHT TO RESTRICTION OF PROCESSING
You have the right to obtain from us restriction of processing where one of the following applies: (a) the
accuracy of the Personal Data is contested by you, for a period enabling us to verify the accuracy of the
Personal Data, (b) the processing is unlawful and you oppose the erasure of the Personal Data and request
the restriction of their use instead, (c) Auctus no longer needs the Personal Data for the purposes of the
processing, but is required by you for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims, (d) you have
objected to processing pending the verification whether the legitimate grounds of Auctus override those of
you.
Where processing has been restricted in accordance with the above, such Personal Data shall, with the
exception of storage, only be processed with your consent or for the establishment, exercise or defense of
legal claims or for the protection of the rights of another natural or legal person or for reasons of important
public interest of the law. If you obtain restriction of processing pursuant to the above, you shall be
informed by Auctus before the restriction of processing is lifted.
18. CONTACT
Questions, comments and request regarding this Privacy Policy are welcomed and should be assessed to
contact@auctus.org​ or through the Telegram group.
19. CHILDREN’S PRIVACY
                                                                                                                7

Our Website is not intended for the use of children (under 18 years old). We do not knowingly market to, or
solicit data from children. We shall not knowingly process, collect of use Personal Data of children, and in
case we receive such data, we shall erase it within a reasonable timeframe.
                                                                                                           8
